(Sheldon:)I did not mean to gaze upon you
as you comb your hair.
(Lalita:)I'm sorry?
(Sheldon:)You are the living embodiment
of the beautiful Princess Panchali.
Oh, no kidding. Who is that?
(Sheldon:)A beloved character
from an Indian folktale.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Oh.
(Lalita:)Us Indian
or "come to our casino" Indian?
- You Indian.
- Oh.
(Sheldon:)The resemblance is remarkable.
(Sheldon:)I can practically smell the lotus blossoms
woven into your ebony hair.
Well, thanks.
(Lalita:)I imagine you smell very nice too.
(Sheldon:)I shower twice a day
and wash my hands as often as I can.
Really? So do I.
(Raj:)But you're a dentist, he's nuts.
(Lalita:)Don't be insulting, Rajesh.
(Lalita:)So, Sheldon, tell me more about
this princess you say I look like.
(Sheldon:)It was said that the gods
fashioned her eyes out of the stars...
(Sheldon:)...and that roses were ashamed to bloom
in the presence of her ruby lips.